A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1987-1988
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series IV: Background Material for Speeches
  - Virginia Community College System--Annual Meeting Meeting 1985 Nov 8 (Box 55)
  - Virginia Meeting Foundation 1985 Sep 14 (Box 55)
  - Virginia Foundation-- Foundation Humanities Program-- Supreme Court and Bill of Rights 1987 Feb 17 (Box 55)
  - Religious Freedom Dinner Symposium 1985 Sep 20 (Box 55)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation and Bryant Hall Dedication 1985 Sep 14 (Box 55)
  - West End Rotary Luncheon (Richmond) 1986 Aug 27 (Box 55)
  - Women Faculty and Professional Association--Luncheon Speaker 1986 Oct 16 (Box 55)
  - Worrell--Management Conference 1986 (Box 55)
- Series V: Restricted Materials (Box Boxes 56-57)